We've trained for years in this laying sword array. Our sword energy is flawless. Yet we couldn't even scratch him.
This demon lord is invincible. If we don't kill him today, the world will be doomed.
See that man in the block below? He's pretty weak, but good for practice. Go beat him, and today's lesson is done.
He's weak? But those three couldn't even touch him.
Eh, well they're even weaker. Go on. Go.
Just go.
Hmm.
Shouldn't even take two hits. Pretty weak.
Thank you, Master. May I know your name?
Master? I just beat a weakling.
He just called the demon lord.
Week?
Find out who that Master is.
Anyone with information will be rewarded by the Celestial Academy.
You go search for him too.
If he joins Soompay's set, all our secret manuals are here to take.
Thornbrose said go.
If this Master is willing to join us, all of the evil decided are his to choose the hardest.
Myself included.
Uh.
Yannick, I was surprised it took you two moves to beat that guy in black.
It's a bit long. You can do better.
Oh, pathetic.
Yes. I'll take your advice.
Masters, I've trained here for eight years. Back then before I came here,
I dreamed of joining a sect called Celestial Academy.
Now, the Desenial Disciple Trial's are starting soon.
Though I'm still weak, I'd like to give it a shot.
Is that so? You want to join them?
Hey, come on, having a vision is good thing.
He's still young. We can't have him with us forever.
Yannick, go for it.
But remember, no matter where you go, we three will always have your back.
Thank you, Masters.
You, Brett. Here, take this.
Hey, you idiot.
This is Laura Fortune Nautis's treasure.
You better keep it safe.
All right, Yannick, go on.
Go on.
Go on, go on, go on, go on.
That token commands infinite wealth and he scoffs at it.
Once Yannick's left, things are about to get wild.